BRADY MENSWAR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Rockledge

PHONE

321-365-2356

EMAIL

bradymenswar@gmail.com

LINKS

Portfolio

<u>GitHub</u>

LinkedIn

SKILLS

React

JavaScript

CSS

HTML5

TailwindCSS

C/C++

SQL

Python

Node.js

Git

Agile Scrum

Cyber Security

Penetration Testing

PROFILE

I am a web developer and software engineer. I am experienced with working on an Agile team with daily Scrum meetings and have worked well with project managers. I've practiced extensively with programming languages such as C++ and JavaScript and have experience with web design components such as CSS, HTML, React, and Vue. I also have worked thoroughly in penetration testing and cybersecurity. I am a new graduate from the University of Florida with a degree in Computer Science.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Designer, Let's Design Your Site

Remote

Apr 2022 — Dec 2022

Worked as a web designer for business owners in need. Based on their vision I put together end-user ready websites. Some of the skills needed for this position are:

- · Web Design
- · SEO
- · Client Relations
- · Inter-Team Communications

Freelance Web Developer, JH Darbie & Co.

Remote

Jan 2023 — Present

Created a company website by working directly with the clients on what they wanted to achieve. Worked as a solo developer and managed all of the infrastructure, communications, and actual development of the website.

- · Client Relations
- · Web Development
- · Time Management
- Communication

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science in Computer Science, University of Florida

Gainesville

May 2019 — May 2023

3.5 GPA